IANNA, HIIDOO HELEN

Kosofe road Block 43, flat 4 Dolphin estate Ikoyi Lagos | +2348036446988 | hiidooianna@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

A creative, analytical and enthusiast individual with over four years' experience across administration and internship with competencies in delivering outstanding and effective managerial, sales promotion and customer relationship services in any self-challenging work environment. Aim at deploying my competencies, skills, and personal values in effecting changes in my immediate work environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

IT Sales & Support officer at Netlinks solutions: Mar. 2023 – Sep 2023

- Reporting any unusual PCs activities to supervisors.
- o Performing data entry duties regarding metrics, sales figures and other key data.
- o Aiding management team members and executives as needed.
- Office 365 mail support such as mail retrieval and mail setup.
- Troubleshooting of windows PCs and upgrades.
- Maintaining an accessible and organized filing system for sales and administrative professionals.

Sales Representative at MoboVet Veterinary services Wurukum Makurdi June. 2021- Dec. 2022

- Execute outbound and inbound sales activities to generate new leads and opportunities.
- Engage with potential clients through various communication channels to understand their needs and offer tailored solutions.
- Grow the MoboVet Veterinary business by using innovative sales and marketing concepts to achieve assigned goals in all key measures
- Achieve and exceed monthly and quarterly sales targets.

Admin Assistant (NYSC) at Nigeria Agricultural Quarantine Service. Mar. 2020 – Mar. 2021

- o Documentation and organization of office files and equipment
- o Typing and printing of documents such as memos, drafts, and correspondence.
- o Being a point of contact for a range of staff and visitors.
- o Welcoming and directing visitors and new staff of the organization.
- o Issuing mails to team and departments as ordered by senior staff.

Intern at University of Agriculture Teaching and Research Farm. June 2017 – May 2018

- o Performing manual farm practices.
- o Managing farm workers and activities.
- Devising strategies for harvesting or breeding.

CORE SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES:

Interpersonal skills | Communication Proficiency | Attention to details | Problem solving | Creative and analytical skills | Decision Making | Time Management | Multitasking | Financial Management | Cost Minimization | Teamwork | Technology savvy | Proficient in Microsoft office tools.

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIP/ASSOCIATION:

- Nigeria Institute of Animal Science.
- o International organization of Management Professionals.

CERTIFICATIONS:

- o Certificate of National Service at National Youth Service Corps. 2021
- o Certificate of Course completion in Project Management. 2020

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS:

- o **B.Agric. Animal Production (Optional)** at Federal University of Agriculture, Makurdi. 2018
- o Senior Secondary Certificate Examination at Regina Pacis College, Abuja. 2012

Referees:

Available upon request.